<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2011-2018 The MathWorks, Inc. -->
<rsccat version="1.0" locale="en_US" product="MATLAB">
  <message>
    <entry key="FourPtsForTetErrId">At least four input points must be provided to define a tetrahedral mesh.</entry>
    <entry key="ThreePtsForTriErrId">At least three input points must be provided to define a triangular mesh.</entry>
    <entry key="FreeBoundaryInvalidMeshErrId">Cannot compute free boundary. The mesh may be invalid.</entry>
    <entry key="ConstrainEmptyErrId">Cannot impose constraints on an empty triangulation.</entry>
    <entry key="DeletePartialConsErrId">Cannot partially delete a constraint.</entry>
    <entry key="DeletePartialPointErrId">Cannot partially delete a point.</entry>
    <entry key="ReducePointsDimErrId">Cannot reduce the dimensionality of the points.</entry>
    <entry key="TwoColConsErrId">Constraints must be defined by two columns defining the start and end points of each edge constraint.</entry>
    <entry key="MixDimDataPtCoordsErrId">Data point coordinates have inconsistent dimension.</entry>
    <entry key="MixDimDataPtErrId">Data points have incompatible dimension.</entry>
    <entry key="ComplexDataPointErrId">Data points in complex number format are not supported.\nUse REAL and IMAG to extract the real and imaginary components.</entry>
    <entry key="SparseDataPtErrId">Data points in sparse matrix format are not supported.</entry>
    <entry key="NonTwoDEdgeConsErrId">Edge constraints can only be assigned to 2D triangulations.</entry>
    <entry key="BadNumArgsDelaunayErrId">Incorrect number of arguments for Delaunay.</entry>
    <entry key="BadNumArgsInterpErrId">Incorrect number of arguments for {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="LocationBadDimErrId">Input data point locations have invalid dimension. The data must be specified in column-vector format.</entry>
    <entry key="ValueNonColVecErrId">Input data point values must be specified in column-vector format.</entry>
    <entry key="LocValueNonColVecErrId">Input data must be specified in column-vector format.</entry>
    <entry key="ValueBadDimErrId">Input data point values have invalid dimension. The data must be specified in column-vector format.</entry>
    <entry key="PointsBadDimErrId">Input points have invalid dimension.</entry>
    <entry key="OOMemDelaunayTriErrId">Insufficient memory available to perform {0} operation.</entry>
    <entry key="BadAssignArgsErrId">Invalid arguments in assignment operation.</entry>
    <entry key="BadIndexArgsErrId">Invalid arguments in indexing operation.</entry>
    <entry key="BadArgInterpEvalErrId">Invalid arguments specified in evaluating the interpolant.</entry>
    <entry key="BadArgsQueryTriErrId">Invalid arguments specified in querying triangulation.</entry>
    <entry key="BadFormatDelaunayTriErrId">Invalid data format for {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="BadFormatInterpValuesErrId">Invalid format for scattered data values.</entry>
    <entry key="BadIndexIntoTriangErrId">Invalid indexing into the triangulation, use the size method to check the dimensions.</entry>
    <entry key="BadIndexIntoXErrId">Invalid indices into property X.</entry>
    <entry key="BadIndexIntoConsErrId">Invalid indices into the Constraints property.</entry>
    <entry key="BadIndexIntoValsErrId">Invalid indices into the values property - V.</entry>
    <entry key="BadInterpTypeErrId">Invalid interpolation type specified.</entry>
    <entry key="BadExtrapTypeErrId">Invalid extrapolation type specified.</entry>
    <entry key="BadArgsIndexOpErrId">Invalid number of arguments in indexing operation.</entry>
    <entry key="WrongNumArgsErrId">Invalid number of arguments.</entry>
    <entry key="WrongInputNumArgsErrId">Invalid number of input arguments.</entry>
    <entry key="WrongOutputNumArgsErrId">Invalid number of output arguments.</entry>
    <entry key="BadDelaunayTriEndErrId">Invalid syntax associated with {0}/end.</entry>
    <entry key="BadInterpEndErrId">Invalid syntax associated with {0}/end.</entry>
    <entry key="MixConsReassignErrId">Mismatch in number of constraints reassigned.</entry>
    <entry key="MixPtsReassignErrId">Mismatch in number of points reassigned.</entry>
    <entry key="MixValsReassignErrId">Mismatch in number of values reassigned.</entry>
    <entry key="NNConstrainedErrId">Nearest Neighbor queries cannot be performed on a constrained triangulation.\nTo do this, copy the triangulation and remove the constraints.</entry>
    <entry key="RepConsBadDimErrId">Replacement constraints have incompatible dimension.</entry>
    <entry key="RepCoordsBadRowDimErrId">Replacement coordinates have incompatible row dimension.</entry>
    <entry key="RepCoordsBadColDimErrId">Replacement coordinates have incompatible column dimension.</entry>
    <entry key="RepPtsBadDimErrId">Replacement points have incompatible dimension.</entry>
    <entry key="AssignToTriErrId">Cannot assign values to the triangulation.</entry>
    <entry key="BadPropNameErrId">Assignment to an invalid property name.</entry>
    <entry key="EdgeMixDimErrId">The column-vectors defining the edges have inconsistent dimensions.</entry>
    <entry key="ComplexDimErrId">The dimension cannot be defined in complex number format.</entry>
    <entry key="SparseDimErrId">The dimension cannot be defined in sparse matrix format.</entry>
    <entry key="SparseInputErrId">The input cannot be defined in sparse matrix format.</entry>
    <entry key="BadCoordsDimErrId">The input coordinates do not have the correct dimension.</entry>
    <entry key="InputMixSizeErrId">The input data has inconsistent size.</entry>
    <entry key="NotDblInputErrId">The input must be in double array format.</entry>
    <entry key="PtRangeErrId">The input must contain index values in the range 1 to num-points.</entry>
    <entry key="SxRangeErrId">The input must contain index values in the range 1 to num-Simplices.</entry>
    <entry key="NoComplexInputErrId">The input must contain index values; complex format is invalid.</entry>
    <entry key="NoFractionsErrId">The input must contain index values; entries with fractional parts are invalid.</entry>
    <entry key="IndexSanityErrId">The input must contain index values; entries with Inf, NaN, zero, negative, or fractional parts are not permitted.</entry>
    <entry key="IndexChecksErrId">The input must contain index values; Inf, NaN, or negative entries are not permitted.</entry>
    <entry key="BadPointSpecErrId">The input points are specified in an invalid format.</entry>
    <entry key="Non2D3DInputErrId">The input points must be 2D or 3D coordinates in numpoints-by-ndim format.</entry>
    <entry key="NonDblInpPtsErrId">The input points must be a double array.</entry>
    <entry key="NonFloatInpPtsErrId">The input points must be a single or double array.</entry>
    <entry key="NonColVecInpPtsErrId">The input points must be specified in column-vector format.</entry>
	<entry key="EmptyInpPtsErrId">The input points array is empty.</entry>
    <entry key="NonFiniteInputPtsErrId">The coordinates of the input points must be finite values; Inf and NaN are not permitted.</entry>
    <entry key="OneArgOnlyErrId">The input should be a single argument.</entry>
    <entry key="ColVecOnlyErrId">The input should be in column-vector format.</entry>
    <entry key="NumEdgBy2FormatErrId">The input should be in numedges-by-2 format.</entry>
    <entry key="ComplexTriErrId">The input triangulation cannot be defined in complex number format.</entry>
    <entry key="SparseTriErrId">The input triangulation cannot be defined in sparse matrix format.</entry>
    <entry key="EmptyInputTriErrId">The input triangulation is empty.</entry>
    <entry key="BadVxIdTriInputErrId">The input triangulation is invalid. It refers to a point index that exceeds the number of points given.</entry>
    <entry key="NotNumtetBy4ErrId">The input triangulation is invalid. The data must be in numtetrahedra-by-4 format.</entry>
    <entry key="NotNumtriBy3ErrId">The input triangulation is invalid. The data must be in numtriangles-by-3 format.</entry>
    <entry key="NotNumsxByNvErrId">The input triangulation is invalid. The data must be in numtriangles-by-3 or numtetrahedra-by-4 format.</entry>
    <entry key="TriNotDblErrId">The input triangulation must be in double array format.</entry>
    <entry key="TriSanityErrId">The input triangulation must contain finite positive values; Inf, NaN, zero, or negative entries are not permitted.</entry>
    <entry key="TriIndexNotIntErrId">The input triangulation must contain index values. Entries with fractional parts are invalid.</entry>
    <entry key="InterpOutOfSyncErrId">The interpolant is in an invalid state.\nThe number of data point locations should equal the number of data point values.</entry>
    <entry key="BadNumBaryErrId">The number of barycentric coordinates per point is invalid.</entry>
    <entry key="NumpNumvErrId">The number of data point locations should equal the number of data point values.</entry>
    <entry key="BalanceConversionErrId">The number of points to convert should equal the number of corresponding simplices.</entry>
    <entry key="QueryPtDimMixupErrId">The query points have inconsistent spatial dimension.</entry>
    <entry key="DimNotDblErrId">The specified dimension must be in double array format.</entry>
    <entry key="DimNotFiniteErrId">The specified dimension must contain finite positive values; Inf, NaN, or negative entries are not permitted.</entry>
    <entry key="DimNotIdxErrId">The specified dimension must be in index values.</entry>
    <entry key="AngInRangeErrId">The threshold angle should be in the range (0, pi).</entry>
    <entry key="TriIsEmptyErrId">The triangulation is empty.</entry>
    <entry key="ConstrainedOnlyErrId">This feature is restricted to 2D constrained Delaunay triangulations.</entry>
    <entry key="TrisOnlyErrId">This feature only supports triangulations composed of triangles.</entry>
    <entry key="NotEnoughPtsConvhullErrId">Error computing the convex hull. Not enough unique points specified.</entry>
    <entry key="EmptyConvhull2DErrId">Error computing the convex hull. The points may be collinear.</entry>
    <entry key="EmptyConvhull3DErrId">Error computing the convex hull. The points may be coplanar or collinear.</entry>
    <entry key="BadOptionsSpecErrId" note="stringDatatypeUpdate">OPTIONS should be a cell array of character vectors.</entry>
    <entry key="OOMemConvexHullErrId">Insufficient memory available to perform convex hull computation.</entry>
    <entry key="ReusableStatusErrId">The reusable status does not match the expected reusable status for in-place optimization testing.</entry>
    <entry key="BadConvhullOptionErrId">Invalid option in argument list.</entry>
    <entry key="BadArgsErrId">Invalid arguments - the input does not match the allowable argument specification.</entry>
    <entry key="NotEnoughPtsDelaunayErrId">Error computing the Delaunay triangulation. Not enough unique points specified.</entry>
    <entry key="OOMemDelaunayErrId">Insufficient memory available to perform Delaunay computation.</entry>
    <entry key="EmptyDelaunay2DErrId">Error computing the Delaunay triangulation. The points may be collinear.</entry>
    <entry key="EmptyDelaunay3DErrId">Error computing the Delaunay triangulation. The points may be coplanar or collinear.</entry>
    <entry key="BadPtAssnWrtConsIdsErrId">Insufficient number of points specified, existing constraints cannot be enforced. Revise the constraints before replacing the points.</entry>
    <entry key="PrivatePropertyErrId">Cannot access private property.</entry>
    <entry key="NotNdGridErrId">Data is not valid NDGRID format.</entry>
    <entry key="NdgridNotMeshgrid2DErrId">\nData is in MESHGRID format, NDGRID format is required.\nConvert your data as follows:\n   X = X'; Y = Y'; V = V'; F = griddedInterpolant(X,Y,V)\n</entry>
    <entry key="NdgridNotMeshgrid3DErrId">\nData is in MESHGRID format, NDGRID format is required.\nConvert your data as follows:\n   P = [2 1 3];\n   X = permute(X, P);\n   Y = permute(Y, P);\n   Z = permute(Z, P);\n   V = permute(V, P);\n   F = griddedInterpolant(X,Y,Z,V)\n</entry>
    <entry key="MixedGridCoordSizeErrId">Grid coordinate arrays have inconsistent size.</entry>
    <entry key="NumCoordsGridNdimsMismatchErrId">The number of input coordinate arrays does not equal the number of dimensions (NDIMS) of these arrays.</entry>
    <entry key="OneDInterpNonVectorErrId">1D interpolation requires vector input for X and V.</entry>
    <entry key="NonMonotonicGridErrId">The grid must be created from grid vectors which are strictly monotonically increasing.</entry>
    <entry key="NonMonotonicCompVecsErrId">The grid vectors must be strictly monotonically increasing.</entry>
    <entry key="NonUniqueGridPtsErrId">The grid must be created from grid vectors which contain unique points.</entry>
    <entry key="NonUniqueCompVecsPtsErrId">The grid vectors must contain unique points.</entry>
    <entry key="NonMonotonic1DErrId">The point coordinates are not sequenced in strict monotonic order.</entry>
    <entry key="BadGridErrId">Grid is improperly defined.</entry>
    <entry key="CompVecValueMismatchErrId">The grid vectors do not define a grid of points that match the given values.</entry>
    <entry key="GridIndexAssignErrId">Indexed assignment into the GridVectors is not supported.\nComplete replacement of GridVectors can be carried out as follows:\n    F = griddedInterpolant(. . .)\n    F.GridVectors = GridVectorsnew\n</entry>
    <entry key="ValueIndexAssignErrId">Indexed assignment into the Values is not supported.\nComplete replacement of Values can be carried out as follows:\n    F = griddedInterpolant(. . .)\n    F.Values = Valuesnew\n</entry>
    <entry key="BadGridInterpEndErrId">Invalid syntax associated with griddedInterpolant/end.</entry>
    <entry key="SparseInterpValuesErrId">Sample values in sparse matrix format is not supported.</entry>
    <entry key="NonFloatValuesErrId">Sample values must be a single or double array.</entry>
    <entry key="NonDoubleValuesErrId">Sample values must be a double array.</entry>
    <entry key="GridInterpOutOfSyncErrId">The interpolant is in an invalid state.\nThe size of the grid is not consistent with the size of the value array.</entry>
    <entry key="InsufficientPoints1DErrId">At least 2 data points are required to create a 1D interpolant.</entry>
    <entry key="InsufficientGridPointsErrId">Grid arrays of at least size 2 in each dimension are required to create an ND interpolant.</entry>
    <entry key="GridOfMixedDataTypesErrId">Grid coordinates must be of the same type, single or double.</entry>
    <entry key="QueryOfMixedDataTypesErrId">Query coordinates must be of the same type, single or double.</entry>
    <entry key="NonVecCompVecErrId">Grid vector is not properly defined.</entry>
    <entry key="CellOfValuesErrId">Sample values cannot be expressed in cell array format.</entry>
    <entry key="NonCellCompVecErrId">Replacement Grid Vectors must be in cell array format.</entry>
    <entry key="OOMemGridInterpErrId">Cannot construct a griddedInterpolant - insufficient memory available.</entry>
    <entry key="OOMemGridInterpEvalErrId">Cannot evaluate the griddedInterpolant - insufficient memory available.</entry>
    <entry key="OOMemGridInterpAssignErrId">Cannot modify the griddedInterpolant - insufficient memory available.</entry>
    <entry key="LoopConsWarnId">Constraint with the same start and end indices - constraint ignored. Duplicate data points have been detected and removed - corresponding values have been averaged.</entry>
    <entry key="DupPtsAvValuesWarnId">Duplicate data points have been detected and removed - corresponding values have been averaged.</entry>
    <entry key="DupPtsWarnId">Duplicate data points have been detected and removed.\n The Triangulation indices are defined with respect to the unique set of points in {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="DupPtsConsUpdatedWarnId">Duplicate data points have been detected and removed.\n The Triangulation indices and constraints are defined with respect to the unique set of points in {0}.</entry>
    <entry key="DupConsWarnId">Duplicate edge constraints have been detected and removed.</entry>
    <entry key="ConsSplitPtWarnId">Edge constraints have been split by a coincident point.</entry>
    <entry key="TooFewPtsInterpWarnId">Insufficient number of data points to create a triangulation-based interpolant.</entry>
    <entry key="ConsConsSplitWarnId">Intersecting edge constraints have been split, this may have added new points into the triangulation.</entry>
    <entry key="DupConsOnEditWarnId">Some constraints were not edited to avoid duplicates.</entry>
    <entry key="DupPtOnEditWarnId">Some data points were not edited - they cannot be moved to duplicate locations.</entry>
    <entry key="PtsNotInTriWarnId">Some input points are not referenced by the triangulation.</entry>
    <entry key="EmptyTri2DWarnId">The triangulation is empty - the points may be collinear.</entry>
    <entry key="EmptyTri3DWarnId">The triangulation is empty - the points may be coplanar or collinear.</entry>
    <entry key="InterpEmptyTri2DWarnId">The underlying triangulation is empty - the points may be collinear.</entry>
    <entry key="InterpEmptyTri3DWarnId">The underlying triangulation is empty - the points may be coplanar or collinear.</entry>
    <entry key="NotConsPolygonWarnId">This feature is only relevant for 2D constrained\n Delaunay triangulations of geometric domains.</entry>
    <entry key="DeprecatedQhullOptionsConvhull">CONVHULL no longer supports or requires Qhull-specific options.\n Please remove these options when calling CONVHULL.</entry>
    <entry key="DeprecatedQhullOptionsDelaunay">DELAUNAY no longer supports or requires Qhull-specific options.\n Please remove these options when calling DELAUNAY.</entry>
    <entry key="DupPtsDelaunayWarnId">Duplicate data points have been detected and removed.\n Some point indices will not be referenced by the triangulation.</entry>
    <entry key="NonPersConstraintsWarnId">Creating a {0} using a constrained Delaunay triangulation.\nThe constraints will be lost if the {1} is saved and loaded.\nTo preserve the constraints save the {2} and recreate {3} after loading.</entry>
    <entry key="CubicNeedsThreeWarnId">The ''cubic'' method requires at least 3 points in each dimension.\nReverting to the default ''linear'' method because this condition is not met.</entry>
    <entry key="Pchip1DonlyWarnId">The ''pchip'' method is only supported in 1D.\nReverting to the default ''linear'' method because this condition is not met.</entry>
    <entry key="CubicUniformOnlyWarnId">The ''cubic'' method requires the grid to have a uniform spacing.\nSwitching the method from ''cubic'' to ''spline'' because this condition is not met.</entry>
    <entry key="MeshgridEval2DWarnId">Query data is in MESHGRID format, NDGRID format will yield better performance.\nConvert your query data (Xq, Yq) as follows:\n   F = griddedInterpolant(. . .);\n   Xq = Xq'; Yq = Yq';\n   Vq = F(Xq,Yq); \n</entry>
    <entry key="MeshgridEval3DWarnId">Query data is in MESHGRID format, NDGRID format will yield better performance.\nConvert your query data (Xq, Yq, Zq) as follows:\n   F = griddedInterpolant(. . .);\n   P = [2 1 3];\n   Xq = permute(Xq, P);\n   Yq = permute(Yq, P);\n   Zq = permute(Zq, P);\n   Vq = F(Xq,Yq,Zq);\n</entry>
    <entry key="DegenerateGridErrId">Interpolation requires at least two sample points in each dimension.</entry>
    <entry key="BadAssignMethodErrId" note="stringDatatypeUpdate">Method must be a valid character vector</entry>
    <entry key="BadAssignExtrapErrId" note="stringDatatypeUpdate">ExtrapolationMethod must be a valid character vector</entry>
    <entry key="NoNaturalExtrapErrId">Natural neighbor extrapolation is not supported, use linear or nearest.</entry>
    <entry key="ScatteredInterpFromDtErrId">Construction from Delaunay triangulation is not supported.\nUse the Delaunay triangulation to perform the interpolation - see documentation.</entry>
    <entry key="CascadingConstraintIntersectionsErrId">Enforcing Delaunay constraints leads to unstable repeated constraint intersections.\nThis may be due to near coincident intersecting constraints or near duplicate points.</entry>
    <entry key="OverlappingConstraintInconsistencyErrId">Cannot enforce the specified Delaunay constraints.\nThe triangulation may be in an invalid state and should be cleared.\nThis error may be due to overlapping constrained edges.\nTry reducing the constraints to a unique set.</entry>
    <entry key="DupPointsBasicWarnId">Duplicate data points have been detected and removed.</entry>
    <entry key="BadAlphaErrId">Alpha must be a scalar double that is full (nonsparse), real, and nonnegative.</entry>
    <entry key="BadThresholdValueErrId">The threshold must be a scalar double that is full (nonsparse), real, and nonnegative.</entry>
    <entry key="BadThresholdSpellingErrId">Invalid name option, spelling may not be correct.</entry>  
    <entry key="RegionRangeErrId">The REGIONID must be an index in the range 1 to numRegions(SHP).</entry>
    <entry key="TwoDAlphaShapeErrId">This method is only applicable to 2D alpha shapes.</entry>
    <entry key="ThreeDAlphaShapeErrId">This method is only applicable to 3D alpha shapes.</entry>
    <entry key="EmptyAlphaShapeErrId">The alpha shape is empty.</entry>
    <entry key="InvalidStringFormatErrId">Named option has invalid format.</entry>
  	<entry key="Next1DonlyWarnId">The ''next'' method is only supported in 1D.\nReverting to the default ''linear'' method because this condition is not met.</entry>
	  <entry key="Previous1DonlyWarnId">The ''previous'' method is only supported in 1D.\nReverting to the default ''linear'' method because this condition is not met.</entry>
	  <entry key="PointLocation2DTriIn3DErrId">Point location is not supported for 2D triangulations in 3D space.</entry>	
    <entry key="ScalarRegionIdErrorId">The REGIONID must be a scalar index in the range 1 to numRegions(SHP) that is full (nonsparse), real, and double.</entry>    	  
    <entry key="BadSpectrumOptionErrId">Invalid name option, spelling may not be correct.</entry>
    <entry key="AlphaShapeNonDoubleErrId" note="stringDatatypeUpdate">Input arguments to alphaShape for points, alpha value, and threshold values, if specified, must be full (nonsparse), real, and double. For Name-Value pairs, the Name should be a character vector.</entry>
    <entry key="FileNotFound"> The specified file could not be found.</entry>
    <entry key = "FileIOError"> File Input Output Error was encountered</entry>
  </message>
</rsccat>
